http://www.hifisoundconnection.com/privacy-policy

Brands
Car AudioAmplifiersSubwoofersSpeakersEnclosures UnloadedCustom Fit EnclosuresCar Audio PackagesEnclosures LoadedVehicle Specific SpeakersAmp & Sub CombosATV SpeakersSee All See More In-Dash ReceiversFactory RadioSignal ProcessorsKick PanelsUTV Side by Side SpeakersMotorcycle SpeakersCar Adapters & Power InvertersSee Less Car Audio Accessories12 Volt Power SuppliesAmp KitsAntennasCoversCircuit BreakersInstallation AccessoriesPower Door KitsRemoval ToolsSpeaker Cover Grilles & BafflesTube Mounting StrapsSee All See More BatteriesBattery isolatorCapacitorsCar Adapters & Power InvertersCar Security & Remote StartsCooling FansDash KitsDistribution BlocksFuse HoldersFusesInstallation AdaptersInstallation HarnessInstallation InterfacesInterconnectsiPod SolutionsJumper CablesLight SystemsMeters & TestersNeon LightingOEM HarnessSignal Path DevicesSound DampingSpeaker Box FabricSpeaker RingsSubwoofer GrillsTerminalsVehicle Specific AntennasVehicle Specific Radio KitsWire HarnessesWiringZune SolutionsSee Less Mobile VideoHeadrest MonitorsAudio & Video AccessoriesSurveillance & Security CamerasHitch & License Plate CamerasOverhead MonitorsRearview Mirror MonitorsVideo Installation PartsSee Less
Marine AudioAccessories & RemotesMarine PackagesJetski SpeakersMarine AmplifiersMarine In-Dash ReceiversMarine SpeakersMarine SubsSpeaker EnclosuresSee Less
Pro LightingArea EffectsDMX Controllers & CablesLightingLighting PackagesMounting Hardware Cases Bags & StandsVideo Projectors & ScreensSee Less
Musical InstrumentsAcoustic GuitarAmp Parts & AccessoriesApparels & GearsBass GuitarElectric GuitarElectronic DrumsGuitar Amp HeadsGuitar Amp & Cabinet PackagesGuitar AmplifiersGuitar Amplifiers CombosSee All See More Guitar Equipment CasesGuitar Speaker CabinetsInstrument CasesInstrument Parts & AccessoriesKeyboard AmplifiersKeyboards & PianosPercussionStands Cables & ClampsStompboxes & FootswitchesStringsUkuleleSee Less Pro AudioAccessoriesAmplifiersAudio Signal ProcessingCables Plugs & AdaptersCases & BagsDJ EquipmentEqualizers & CrossoversHeadphonesMixersMusic ProductionSee All See More PA SpeakersPA SystemsPower ConditioningRecording EquipmentReplacement SpeakersReplacement SubwoofersSound SystemsStands - RacksWired MicrophonesWireless MicrophonesSee Less
Home TheaterAudio & Video AccessoriesTelevisions & ProjectorsTurntablesSee Less Home Theater AccessoriesCablesCleaning KitsInterconnectsLCD & Plasma TV BracketsStructured WiringWall PlatesSee Less
CloseoutsAccessoriesAmplifiersCar Performance PartsHome TheaterMarine AudioMobile VideoPro AudioSpeakersSee Less
105% Low Price Guarantee
Ships same day if ordered before 3pm CST
Free shipping to 48 States. See details...
Free shipping to 48 States. Ships same day if ordered before 3pm CST. See details...
Privacy Policy
HiFiSoundconnection.com (hereinto referred as “the company”, “we”, “our” and “us”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, its customer relations management system (CMS) and order management system (OMS). It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through this website by purchasing any item sold herein or from marketplaces (collectively called “platform” herein) where we sold our products, what is retained and needed by our CMS and OMS, and how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How can you correct any inaccuracies in the information
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site or from a platform in which we sell our products you purchase. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via our order form in this website, email or other direct contact from you.
Additionally, we may have access to your information you already shared with consent with a platform where you buy our products from. This information, however, are limited only to what is given by the platform, and mostly needed only for shipping purposes and only in a “need-to-know” basis. We are also bound by the platform’s data protection policies and agreed to comply with its acceptable use policies, and to protect your data at all cost.
We will use your information to inform you of your order’s status, and its shipment progress; or to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us in case of phone, email or chat inquiries; or to verify information in case of customer service support requests.
In all cases, we will not disclose this information to anyone outside of the company, unless required by law. We also do not sell or rent your information to anyone.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following by contacting us via the email address or phone number given at the end of this page:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information at all cost. When you submit sensitive information via this website or the platform where you by our products from, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way through utilizing the best encrypting algorithms and standards there is in the data security industry (we currently use TLS 1.2 through HTTPS). You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of https://www.hifisoundconnection.com. Also, we do not store your credit card information.
In addition, the company and this website’s data and network security practices are periodically audited by industry-trusted third-party information security companies, such as Trustwave. This is to ensure that the company and our systems are fully PCI-compliant all the time.
Only employees who need the information (in a “need-to-know” basis) to perform a specific job (e.g., billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
We strictly comply when platforms require us that we remove any personally identifiable information we collected from them in our systems after a certain period. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information when at rest and when it is backed up for offline archiving. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information at rest and offline are kept in a secure environment and are AES-256-encrypted.
How to Contact us About your Data
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, or the platform’s data security and privacy policies, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-877-275-4434 or via email at
with the subject “DATA PRIVACY REQUEST”.
Categories
Car Audio
Marine Audio
Pro Lighting
DJ & Pro Audio
Home Audio & Portables
Closeouts
Brands
Car Audio
Car AudioAmplifiersSubwoofersSpeakersEnclosures UnloadedCustom Fit EnclosuresCar Audio PackagesEnclosures LoadedVehicle Specific SpeakersAmp & Sub CombosATV SpeakersSee All See More In-Dash ReceiversFactory RadioSignal ProcessorsKick PanelsUTV Side by Side SpeakersMotorcycle SpeakersCar Adapters & Power InvertersSee Less Car Audio Accessories12 Volt Power SuppliesAmp KitsAntennasCoversCircuit BreakersInstallation AccessoriesPower Door KitsRemoval ToolsSpeaker Cover Grilles & BafflesTube Mounting StrapsSee All See More BatteriesBattery isolatorCapacitorsCar Adapters & Power InvertersCar Security & Remote StartsCooling FansDash KitsDistribution BlocksFuse HoldersFusesInstallation AdaptersInstallation HarnessInstallation InterfacesInterconnectsiPod SolutionsJumper CablesLight SystemsMeters & TestersNeon LightingOEM HarnessSignal Path DevicesSound DampingSpeaker Box FabricSpeaker RingsSubwoofer GrillsTerminalsVehicle Specific AntennasVehicle Specific Radio KitsWire HarnessesWiringZune SolutionsSee Less Mobile VideoHeadrest MonitorsAudio & Video AccessoriesSurveillance & Security CamerasHitch & License Plate CamerasOverhead MonitorsRearview Mirror MonitorsVideo Installation PartsSee Less
Marine AudioAccessories & RemotesMarine PackagesJetski SpeakersMarine AmplifiersMarine In-Dash ReceiversMarine SpeakersMarine SubsSpeaker EnclosuresSee Less
Pro LightingArea EffectsDMX Controllers & CablesLightingLighting PackagesMounting Hardware Cases Bags & StandsVideo Projectors & ScreensSee Less
Musical InstrumentsAcoustic GuitarAmp Parts & AccessoriesApparels & GearsBass GuitarElectric GuitarElectronic DrumsGuitar Amp HeadsGuitar Amp & Cabinet PackagesGuitar AmplifiersGuitar Amplifiers CombosSee All See More Guitar Equipment CasesGuitar Speaker CabinetsInstrument CasesInstrument Parts & AccessoriesKeyboard AmplifiersKeyboards & PianosPercussionStands Cables & ClampsStompboxes & FootswitchesStringsUkuleleSee Less Pro AudioAccessoriesAmplifiersAudio Signal ProcessingCables Plugs & AdaptersCases & BagsDJ EquipmentEqualizers & CrossoversHeadphonesMixersMusic ProductionSee All See More PA SpeakersPA SystemsPower ConditioningRecording EquipmentReplacement SpeakersReplacement SubwoofersSound SystemsStands - RacksWired MicrophonesWireless MicrophonesSee Less
Home TheaterAudio & Video AccessoriesTelevisions & ProjectorsTurntablesSee Less Home Theater AccessoriesCablesCleaning KitsInterconnectsLCD & Plasma TV BracketsStructured WiringWall PlatesSee Less
CloseoutsAccessoriesAmplifiersCar Performance PartsHome TheaterMarine AudioMobile VideoPro AudioSpeakersSee Less
